<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EmmanApp</string>

    <string name="expectations_title">Expectations</string>
    <string name="contributions_title">Contributions</string>
    <string name="motivations_title">Motivations</string>
    <string name="hindrances_title">Hindrances</string>
    <string name="members_title">Members</string>

    <string-array name="expectations">
        <item>We expect to gain more knowledge and understanding that I can apply in both academic and real life.</item>
        <item>We expect to have fun and understand the lessons that will be taught.</item>
        <item>We expect this course to be challenging but also rewarding.</item>
        <item>We also expect to improve our skills and become more confident in applying what we learn.</item>
        <item>We expect to receive constructive feedback that will help us grow and improve.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="contributions">
        <item>We will give our utmost effort in completing assignments and projects on time.</item>
        <item>We will always listen, attend classes, and pass the requirements.</item>
        <item>We will participate and contribute to group activities, and communicate properly.</item>
        <item>We will help organize group work and ensure everyone participates.</item>
        <item>We will maintain a positive attitude and be respectful to our peers and instructor.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="motivations">
        <item>We are motivated by our goal to succeed academically and personally.</item>
        <item>We are motivated because of our family\'s financial status</item>
        <item>We are motivated to pass this course with a satisfactory grade so we can graduate on time.</item>
        <item>We are motivated by our dream to have a stable and fulfilling career in the future.</item>
        <item>We are driven by a genuine interest in the subject and a desire to master new skills.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="hindrances">
        <item>We sometimes struggle with time management because of different responsibilities.</item>
        <item>We love sleeping.</item>
        <item>We also acknowledge that we have many hobbies that may distract us from being productive.</item>
        <item>Sometimes unexpected events or personal problems may also affect our focus and performance.</item>
        <item>We sometimes tend to procrastinate on tasks that we find difficult or overwhelming.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="members">
        <item>Carino, Ian Kyril</item>
        <item>Gaddi, Noel</item>
        <item>Molina, Trisha</item>
        <item>Recondo, Juan Miguel</item>
        <item>Tungcul, Marjorie</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>